Guide to the William Saroyan Papers, 1926-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Correspondence, ca. 1926-1981, Series 1
  - I miscellany, 1.17
    - Ilic - Imura (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - In - Indiana Univ. Press (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Infantry - Insight (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Institute - Insurance (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Intendant - International Cultural (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - International Editors - International Poetry (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - International T - Intravaia (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Io - Israelite (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Italian - Ivry (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - I primary, 1.18
    - Ince, Alexander,1946; 1952, 5 items: 1 from WS (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - International Communication Agency,1979-80, 10 items (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - International Herald Tribune1974-78, 45 items: 22 from WS (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - International Herald Tribune1979-80, 29 items: 12 from WS (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Irbe, Elza,1970-72; 1975-79, 24 items: 4 from WS (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Irish Press,1952; 1975-78; 1980-81, 29 items: 12 from WS (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Irving, Jules,1969; 1972, 11 items: 2 from WS (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Ives, Burl,1965, 2 items: 1 from WS (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Ito, Teiji,1961, 3 items: 1 from WS (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - J miscellany, 1.19
    - Ja - James (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Jamieson - Janes (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Janevesian - Jay (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Je - Jiggerian (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Jo - Johnson, J. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Johnson - Jonathan (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Jones - Joyce (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Judd - Justman (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - J primary, 1.20
    - Jacobson, Helen,1955, 6 items: 1 from WS (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Janes, Jose,1946-66, 37 items: 10 from WS (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Janigian, Bruce,1978-79, 5 items to WS (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Japan Uni Agency,1970-81; n.d., 62 items: 5 from WS (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Jasienko, Jean Michel,1953-61, 31 items: 7 from WS (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Jessel, George,1954-55, 2 items to WS (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Margo,1954-55, 7 items: 4 from WS (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Michael Joseph Ltd.,1970-71, 12 items to WS (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Jugoslovenska Autorska Agencija,1959-73, 24 items: 10 from WS (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - K miscellany, 1.21
    - Ka - Kalaydjian (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Kaldunion - Kanzlit (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Kaplan - Kassouni (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Katchadourian - KCET (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Ke - Kells (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Kelly - Kennedy (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Kennelly - Keosheyan (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Kerman - KFSN (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Kh - Kimmel (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - King - Kiraly (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Kirkeby - Kiwanis (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Khachadourian - Khoulesserian (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Kl - KMJ (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Knadjian - Knox (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Ko - Kolligian (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Kolsoozian - Kozlenko (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kp - KQED (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Kr - Kravette (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Kremer - Krup (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - KS - KTTV (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Kucera - Kuznetsov (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Kx - Ky (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - K primary, 1.22
    - Kalustian, Mark,1980, 8 items: 3 from WS (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Kandel, Boris,1968-71, 11 items: 4 from WS (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Kanin, Garson,1942-76, 9 items: 3 from WS (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Karabian, Walter,1970-76, 20 items: 3 from WS (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Schima,1936, 6 items to WS (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Kazarian, Jacqueline (Papazian),1936-80; n.d., 30 items: 7 from WS (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Keane, Margaret and Walter,1963; 1965; n.d., 12 items: 1 from WS (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Kelikian, Alice,1975-76, 5 items: 2 from WS (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Kelikian, Hampar and Zoom,1934-78, 14 items: 2 from WS (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Kelly, Gene,1942-55, 16 items: 4 from WS (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Kelm, Karlton,1934; 1939; n.d., 8 items to WS (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Kenkyusha Ltd.,1951-78, 16 items: 4 from WS (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - J. F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts,1972; 1979-80, 9 items: 2 from WS (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Kenyon Review,1967-70, 10 items: 5 from WS (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Kerr, Walter,1961, 1 item to WS (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Kerz, Leo,1954-55, 8 items: 3 from WS (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Kesdekian, Mesrop,1954-64, 12 items: 6 from WS (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Kesey, Ken,1976, 1 item to WS (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Keshishian, Levon,1952-55; 1969-72, 25 items: 5 from WS (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Kalmanoff, Martin,1955-56; 1959, 14 items: 1 from WS (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - Kevorkian, Andy,1965-72, 32 items: 4 from WS (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1966-67, 39 items: 14 from WS (Box 50, Folder 2)
      See also: Coudert Frères
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1968, 36 items: 14 from WS (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1969, 26 items: 6 from WS (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1970, 43 items: 8 from WS (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1971, 35 items: 13 from WS (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1972, 33 items: 4 from WS (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1973, 48 items: 15 from WS (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Kevorkian Caldwell1974-81, 46 items: 6 from WS (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Keyishian, Harry,1970-72; 1978-80, 32 items: 8 from WS (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Kherdian, David1963-66, 22 items: 4 from WS (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Kherdian, David1967-79; n.d., 52 items: 10 from WS (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Kingman, Dong,1953-68; n.d., 50 items: 8 from WS (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Kinseido Ltd.,1966-69, 6 items to WS (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Klezmer Corp.,1979-80, 10 items: 1 from WS (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Knight, Goodwin J.,1958, 1 item to WS (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Alfred A. Knopf Inc.,1934-48, 13 items: 2 from WS (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Kolev, Svetoslav,1968-79, 29 items: 2 from WS (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Kornfeld, Anita and John,1979-80, 9 items: 1 from WS (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Kovacheva, Katia,1978, 3 items to WS (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Krakower, Arnold,1950-59, 11 items: 5 from WS (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Krementz, Jill,1974-75, 6 items to WS (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Krim, Seymour,1951-52; 1968, 11 items: 5 from WS (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Kudian, Mischa,1947-78, 21 items: 5 from WS (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - L miscellany, 1.23
    - L.A. - Landau (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Lane - Langsford (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Langworthy - Lass (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Latum - Lazarus (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - League - LeClerc (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Lee - Lehman (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Leigh - Leung (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Levchev - Levitz (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Levonian - Lexington (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Liber - Lichtig (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Liddell - Limited (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Lincoln - Linton (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Lion - Literary Review (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Literatura - Livingston (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Lloyd - Longford (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Longman - Loroth (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles - Los Angeles Welfare (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Lothrop - Lowits (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Lubetsky - Ludlum (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Luhn - Lutheran (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Lycee - Lytell (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - L primary, 1.24
    - La Jolla Playhouse,1951-53, 6 items: 3 from WS (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Ladies Home Journal,1950-77, 55 items: 19 from WS (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Laemmle, Carl,1951-71, 7 items: 2 from WS (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Landers Agency, Inc.,1962-63, 8 items: 1 from WS (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Lang, John,1936, 7 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Lapham, Roger,1947, 3 items: 1 from WS (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - LaPautre, Michelle,1963-80, 23 items: 5 from WS (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Law, Janet,1956, 13 items: 4 from WS (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Lawrence, Seymour,1971; 1980, 4 items: 1 from WS (Box 54, Folder 9)
      See also: Atlantic Monthly Press
    - Lazar, Irving.1949; 1959; 1961, 28 items: 13 from WS (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - League of American Writers,1939, 4 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Leake, Chauncey J.,1951-76, 26 items: 6 from WS (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Learning,1972-78, 19 items: 7 from WS (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Canada,1948, 1 item to WS (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Leeds Music Corp.,1951-62, 17 items: 5 from WS (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Leinsdorff, Erich,1955, 1 item to WS (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Leisure Books, Inc.,1970, 8 items: 3 from WS (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Lerner, Max,1942, 1 item from WS (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - LeRoy, Warner,1960-61, 2 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Leve, Sam,1947; 1971, 7 items: 2 from WS (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Sinclair,1936, 1 item to WS (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Lexington Herald,1980-81, 3 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance Co.,1946; 1953, 7 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Librairie Stock,1960-64, 7 items: 1 from WS (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Liebermann, Rolf,1956, See also: National Broadcasting Corp. (Box 54, Folder 25)
      3 items to WS
    - Liebow, Richard,1957, 1 item to WS (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Life Magazine.1940-69, 33 items: 17 from WS (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - J. B. Lippincott Co.,1949-80, 15 items: 2 from WS (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Lish, Gordon,1965-66, 3 items to WS (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Listening Library1971-73, 47 items: 21 from WS (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Listening Library1974-80, 49 items: 17 from WS (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Little, Brown and Co..1936-76, 62 items: 14 from WS (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Lloyd, Norman,1952-55, 9 items: 1 from WS (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Loeb Loeb,1954-55; 1975, 4 items to WS (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Loesser, Frank,1948; 1951, 4 items: 2 from WS (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Look Magazine,1952-70, See also: Rothstein, Arthur (Box 55, Folder 7)
      26 items: 10 from WS
    - Loring, Eugene,1941-42; 1951, 6 items: 3 from WS (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles County Dental Society,1954, 6 items: 2 from WS (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Lowe, David,1942, 11 items: 4 from WS (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Lowry, Robert,1958, 10 items to WS (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Luce, Claire,1951; 1971, 4 items: 1 from WS (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Luengo, Lucinda (Saroyan),1961-81, 15 items: 3 from WS (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Lundbergh, Holger,1957; 1965; 1976, 6 items to WS (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - A. and S. Lyons, Inc.,1931-48; n.d., 57 items: 19 from WS (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Lyons, Leonard and Sylvia1938-62, 53 items: 17 from WS (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Lyons, Leonard and Sylvia1964-80; n.d., 24 items: 4 from WS (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - M miscellany, 1.25
    - Macalester - McCally (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - McCarthy - McCutcheon (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - MacDonagh - MacEwen (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Macfadyen - McKinney (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - McKowen - McMullin (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - McNeil - McWhorter (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Maddaugh - Madigan (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Madison - Magic (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Magnin - Magyar (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Mahari - Mallet (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Malloy - Manhatten (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Manitoba - Manoukian (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Manuel - Maple (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Marano - Markarian (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Markovic - Marowitz (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Marquis - Marsoobian (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Martin (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Maryland - Massiah (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Masteroff - Matilla (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Matisse - Maxwell (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - May - Mayorga (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Meador - Meltzer (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Memphis - Mentally (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Meramec - Merriman (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Mersand - Metropole (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Meyer (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Miami - Michigan (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Microform - Midlo (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Midtown - Millersburg (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Milligan - Minasian (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Mindel - Miss (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Missakian - MKR (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Mobile - Mollica (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Monitor - Montfort (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery - Mooradian (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Moore - Morrison (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Morrissey - Mowen (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - MS. - Muradian (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Murphy - Mutual (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Myerberg - Myerson (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - M primary, 1.26
    - McCabe, Charles,1972, 3 items: 1 from WS (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - McCalls,1951-78, 60 items: 22 from WS (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - McClanahan, Grant,1968; 1980, 5 items: 1 from WS (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - McClanahan, Marion and Robt. Wernick,1975, 20 items: 5 from WS (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Macdonald, Dwight,n.d., 1 item to WS (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - MacDonald, Phyllis Brooks,1979-80, 10 items: 3 from WS (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - McDougal, Littell Co.1970-71, 24 items: 8 from WS (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - McDougal, Littell Co.1972-75, 29 items: 7 from WS (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - MacGibbon Kee,1968-69, 15 items: 7 from WS (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - McGowan, John,1955, 1 item to WS (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1957-64, 27 items: 4 from WS (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1975 Jan.-Sept., 35 items: 8 from WS (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1975, 33 items: 8 from WS (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1976 Jan.-March, 32 items: 7 from WS (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1976 Apr.-Dec., 39 items: 12 from WS (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co.1977-79; n.d., 21 items: 1 from WS (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - McKeen, Willian,1976, 1 item to WS (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Macleish, Archibald,1954-55, 4 items: 1 from WS (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Macleod, Norman,1951, 5 items to WS (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Macmillan Company1936-68, 39 items: 10 from WS (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Macmillan Company1970-76, 33 items: 10 from WS (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - McPartland, Marian,1957, 1 item to WS (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - MacRae, Gordon,1957, 3 items: 1 from WS (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Mademoiselle,1939; 1951; 1954, 6 items: 3 from WS (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Magazine Management Co.,1955-63, 40 items: 8 from WS (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Mahakian, Karnig,1965-79, 42 items: 4 from WS (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Makasian, Dennis and Jim,1969; 1976-77, 8 items: 3 from WS (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Makasian, Ralph (Buck),1939-80, 74 items: 36 from WS (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Maksian, George,1970; 1978-79, 15 items: 2 from WS (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Malibu (Misc. org.),1952-80, 20 items: 4 from WS (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Mandel, Julie,1960-62, 17 items: 4 from WS (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Manoogian, Kathy1958-69, 46 items: 10 from WS (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Manoogian, Kathy1970, 11 items: 2 from WS (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Manoogian, Kathy1971-76, 14 items: 2 from WS (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - March, Michael,1934-39; n.d., 14 items to WS (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Marcos, Imelda,1975-76, 3 items to WS (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Marcus, Charles and Rosheen,1946-57; n.d., 17 items: 8 from WS (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Mardikian, George1938-49, 41 items: 16 from WS (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Mardikian, George1951-54, 30 items: 14 from WS (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Margossian, Sarkis,1979-80, 10 items: 3 from WS (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Mark 56 Records,1975-78, 6 items: 1 from WS (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Marlin, Max,1951; n.d., 5 items to WS (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Marshall, Herbert,1980, 1 item to WS (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Fletcher.1951-53, 15 items: 9 from WS (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - George Marton Plays,1953-62, See also: Marton, Elizabeth (Box 62, Folder 3)
      39 items: 4 from WS
    - Marton, Elizabeth,1969-77, See also: George Marton Plays (Box 62, Folder 4)
      6 items: 1 from WS
    - Marvin, Mark,1948, 16 items: 5 from WS (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Mason, Phil,1936; 1967-75, 7 items to WS (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Harold Matson Co.1937-39 Sept., 70 items: 24 from WS (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Harold Matson Co.1939 Oct.-Dec., 34 items: 11 from WS (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Harold Matson Co.1940, 43 items to WS (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Harold Matson Co.1941, 44 items: 9 from WS (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Harold Matson Co.1942-49, 70 items: 13 from WS (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Harold Matson Co.1950, 12 items to WS (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Harold Matson Co.1951-52, 33 items: 4 from WS (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Harold Matson Co.1953, 44 items: 10 from WS (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Harold Matson Co.1954, 73 items: 38 from WS (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Harold Matson Co.1955-56, 29 items: 11 from WS (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Harold Matson Co.1957-59, 28 items: 7 from WS (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Harold Matson Co.1960, 30 items: 16 from WS (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Harold Matson Co.1961 Jan.-April, 53 items: 22 from WS (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Harold Matson Co.1961 May-Aug., 52 items: 18 from WS (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Harold Matson Co.1961 Sep.-Dec., 38 items: 12 from WS (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Harold Matson Co.1962; 1965-69, 29 items: 9 from WS (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Jan.-March 21, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Mar. 22-Ap. 15, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Ap. 21-30, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 May, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 June, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 July, 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Aug., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Sept., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Oct., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Nov., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1944 Dec., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1945 Jan.-Feb., 1 volume from WS (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1943-45, 11 items: 6 from WS (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1947, 1 item to WS (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1949, 35 items: 15 from WS (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1950, 45 items: 31 from WS (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1951, 8 items to WS (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1952, 7 items: 2 from WS (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1952, Divorce papers (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1953, 4 items: 1 from WS (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1954, 8 items: 4 from WS (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1954 June-Aug., 46 items: 10 from WS (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1955, 27 items: 9 from WS (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1956, 26 items: 16 from WS (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1957, 5 items: 2 from WS (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1958, 10 items: 3 from WS (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1959, 11 items: 4 from WS (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)1960-62, 5 items: 1 from WS (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Matthau, Carol (Saroyan)n.d., 15 items to WS (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - George Mattingly Graphic Design,1978-79, See also: Creative Arts Book Co. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      11 items: 3 from WS
    - Mayer, Louis B.,1943, 1 item to WS (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - MCA.1946-79, 37 items: 9 from WS (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - MD Publications,1965-66, 25 items: 8 from WS (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Ben Medford Agency,1934-47, 16 items: 2 from WS (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Mencken, H. L.,1936; 1942-47, 11 items: 3 from WS (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Meredith, Burgess,1961, 4 items to WS (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Scott Meredith Literary Agency,1955-75, 37 items: 10 from WS (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Merian,1976-77, 18 items: 6 from WS (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Meridian Productions, Inc.,1954, 6 items to WS (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Messerlian, Zaven,1972-74, 6 items: 1 from WS (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer1934-50, 28 items: 12 from WS (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer1952-54; n.d., 27 items: 8 from WS (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Meyer, Fleur Cowles,1960, 4 items: 1 from WS (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Michaelian (various cousins),1954-76, 10 items to WS (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Michigan State Library,1968, 7 items: 2 from WS (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Arthur,1970, 1 item to WS (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Henry,1936; 1946, 19 items to WS (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Mitch,1956, 1 item to WS (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Mills College,1935; 1947-66, 8 items to WS (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Minasian, Archie1930-38, 42 items: 39 from WS (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Minasian, Archie1940-47, 15 items: 7 from WS (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Minasian, Archie1950-51, 48 items: 25 from WS (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Minasian, Archie1952, 47 items: 19 from WS (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Minasian, Archie1953, 47 items: 15 from WS (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Minasian, Archie1954, 31 items: 8 from WS (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Minasian, Archie1955, 9 items: 1 from WS (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Minasian, Archie1956, 13 items: 2 from WS (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Minasian, Archie1957, 9 items: 4 from WS (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Minasian, Archie1958-59, 9 items: 1 from WS (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Minasian, Archie1961-65, 25 items: 4 from WS (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Minasian, Archie1966-68, 42 items: 14 from WS (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Minasian, Archie1969, 29 items: 13 from WS (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Minasian, Archie1970, 57 items: 18 from WS (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Minasian, Archie1971, 42 items: 11 from WS (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Minasian, Archie1972, 25 items: 6 from WS (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Minasian, Archie1973, 20 items: 6 from WS (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Minasian, Archie1974, 12 items: 4 from WS (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Minasian, Archie1975, 7 items: 2 from WS (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Minasian, Archie1976, 13 items: 3 from WS (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Minasian, Archie1977, 23 items: 8 from WS (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Minasian, Archie1978-79, 24 items: 4 from WS (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Minasian, Archie1980-81; n.d., 19 items: 1 from WS (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Minasian, Frances,1968-70, 4 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Minasian, Kirk1934-57, 19 items: 10 from WS (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Minasian, Kirk1963-80, 20 items: 7 from WS (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Minasian, Vic,1954-80, 8 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Minnelli, Vincente,1939, 4 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Miss Hewitt's Classes,1950-51, 7 items: 1 from WS (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell, Curtis,1963-64, 4 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Mkrchian, Levon,1978-80, 21 items: 2 from WS (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Modern Age Books,1937-39, 31 items: 2 from WS (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Modern Library,1934-36, 10 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Mogull, Ivan,1965, 3 items: 1 from WS (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Momjian, Set Charles,1976-79, 11 items: 3 from WS (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Arnoldo Mondadori Editore,1946-71, 52 items: 13 from WS (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Moody, Helen Wills,1952; 1957; n.d., 5 items to WS (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Moradian, Frank and Roxie1933-51, 23 items: 6 from WS (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Moradian, Frank and Roxie1953-80, 30 items: 7 from WS (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Moradian, Tom,1966-75, 10 items: 1 from WS (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Morgan, Henry,1951, 1 item from WS (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Mori, Toshio,1939-67, 22 items: 5 from WS (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Morley, Frank,1952-69, See also: Dial Press (Box 70, Folder 1)
      6 items: 4 from WS
    - William Morris Agency1934-56, 41 items: 2 from WS (Box 70, Folder 2)